<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BMTM_TURNPHASE_DYN_SIM_MULTI" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dynamic Simultaneous Multi-Turns [Beta]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BMTM_TURNPHASE_DYN_SIM_MULTI_DESC" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This turn mode only makes sense if there is no turn timer. Players at peace take their turns at the same time. Players at war take their civil actions at the same time, but their military actions sequentially (multiple times per turn). Military units cannot attack or move while another player has the control over his military actions, but civil actions are still possible while other players do their military actions. Every war participant has a limited budget of military actions. When it's exhausted, the control over military actions is passed on to the next player. The control over military actions is passed on over and over again until everybody has done all military actions he wants to do and ended his turn. "Multi-Turn" means that war participants will often get control over their military units multiple times per turn in case the budget is not sufficient to do all necessary actions at once, so their may will be an exchange of military strikes between players multiple times per turn. This turn mode adds more tactical depth to warfare between players, as the decision which military actions they do first within a turn will may have an impact on the war outcome. Also, it accelerates war pacing because wait times will be shorter until the next military actions can be done.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BMTM_TURNPHASE_DYN_SIM_SINGLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dynamic Simultaneous Single-Turns [Beta]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BMTM_TURNPHASE_DYN_SIM_SINGLE_DESC" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Players at peace take their turns at the same time. Players at war take their civil actions at the same time, but their military actions sequentially. Military units cannot attack or move while another player has the control over his military actions, but civil actions are still possible while other players do their military actions. Every war participant will do all his military actions at once and has the control over his military actions only once per turn until he decides to pass over the military control to the next player or ends his turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BMTM_TURNPHASE_TWOPHASE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dynamic Two-Phase Turns [Unsupported]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BMTM_TURNPHASE_TWOPHASE_DESC" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Players at peace take their turns at the same time. Players at war undergo two turn phases: First, they do their military actions sequentially. After all players at war completed their military actions, they enter a civil actions phase afterwars. This turn mode was implemented by Firaxis in the code of the game core, but for some reason they decided to not to make it available to players. The BMTM mod activated this hidden turn mode, but it's untested and unsupported. The implementation of this turn mode is not accessible to modders which means possible bugs cannot be fixed by the BMTM mod.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BMTM_MILITARY_ACTIONS_PER_BMTM_TURN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Military Action Limit</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BMTM_MILITARY_ACTIONS_PER_BMTM_TURN_DESC" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The maximum number of military actions each war participant can do before the game hands-over the control of military actions to the next player. The control over military actions is going in turn over and over again until everybody has done all military actions he wants to do and ended his turn.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BMTM_ROTATORY_BMTM_TURN_START" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rotary Military Action Turn Start</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BMTM_ROTATORY_BMTM_TURN_START_DESC" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Defines whether the player who can do military actions first will be changing on each turn. This option can lead to the situation that people can attack 2 times in a row. Anyhow, players can influence whether that could happen by deciding whether they'll attack first or let the other player attack first.</Text>
		</Row>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>